Finding Aid to the Gloria Steinem papers SSC.MS.00237
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VII. SUBJECTS, 1956-96
  - Griffin, Merv: correspondence and printed materials, 1978-80; undated (Box 192, Folder 13)
  - Groesbeck, Arvilla: correspondence, printed material, photographs, 1977; undated (Box 192, Folder 14)
  - Growth Industries: conference packet, 1980 (Box 192, Folder 15)
  - Guerilla Girls: newsletter, clippings, and endorsement by Steinem, 1994 (Box 192, Folder 16)
  - Guggenheim, Elinor: newsletter and memoranda, Child Care Action Campaign, 1983-84 (Box 192, Folder 17)
  - Gunn, David: clippings, 1983 (Box 192, Folder 18)
  - Hall, Pamela: correspondence, 1990-91 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Hanes: correspondence, press releases, clippings, medical task force report, 1983-84 (Box 193, Folder 2-3)
  - Harrington, Michael: correspondence and clippings 1988, 1993 (re: "A Celebration of Michael Harrington") (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Harris, Elizabeth Forsling, text of 1971 Esquire article with rebuttals and miscellany, 1989 (Box 193, Folder 5-6)
  - Harris, Jean: correspondence, 1986 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Health Care: correspondence and reports, 1980 (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Health and Hospital Workers Union (Bread and Roses event): clippings, 1979 (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Hefner, Christie: clippings and Playboy Foundation brochure, 1980; 1982 (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Hernandez, Aileen: research papers, 1975; 1979 (Box 193, Folder 11)
  - Heroines and Healers: correspondence, 1992 (Box 193, Folder 12)
  - Hispanic women: miscellaneous materials, 1977-79 (Box 193, Folder 13)
  - Homes for the Homeless: correspondence, clippings, minutes, and memoranda, 1986-94 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Horbal, Koryne/ 1-900 lobbying number: correspondence, clippings, and memoranda, 1981, 1993 [includes memo from Susan Faludi] (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Hughes, Dorothy Pitman: miscellaneous materials pertaining to Patricia and Angela Hughes (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Human Nature, 1986 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - "Images of Labor" (Bread and Roses), undated (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - Incest project: correspondence, 1988-95 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - India
    - Brochures and pamphlets, 1975 (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - General, pertaining to 1976 trip (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - Indian Cooperative Union: general, 1975 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Indian Council for Child Welfare: bulletins, 1974-75 (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - Indian Council for Social Science Research: publications, 1975 (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - International Women's Year in India: journals, newsletters, and booklet, 1975 (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - Magazines, newspapers, and clippings, 1958-60; 1970-76; undated (Box 195, Folder 1-3)
    - "Papers on the Status and Role of Women in India" (Dr. Neera Desai), undated (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - Inform, Inc.: correspondence and program materials, 1985-86 (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - Institute of Naturopathic Medicine: correspondence and minutes, 1993-94 (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - Interchange: correspondence, minutes and memoranda, clippings, newsletters, 1978-79 (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - Interlink Press Service: agendas, minutes, reports, press materials, by-laws, 1980-81 (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - International Sophrology Institute: press kit, 1980 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - In These Times: correspondence and press materials, 1979 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Invitations (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - Iranian women's movement: miscellaneous research materials, 1979 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Israel: notes, undated (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - Iris: A Journal About Women: correspondence, 1988; 1990 (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - Joint Foundation Support, Inc.: annual report and script, 1977 (Box 196, Folder 7)
  - Kennedy, Edward: correspondence 1987-88 (includes letter from his children to Steinem) (Box 196, Folder 8)
  - Keehn, Martha: funeral program, 1996 (Box 196, Folder 9)
  - Kissinger, Henry: note and letters, 1971 (Box 196, Folder 10)
  - Kollontai, Alexandra: interview with Steinem by Sonia Baevsky and Baevsky's discussion with Barbara Clements, 1976 (Box 196, Folder 11)
  - Kowalski, Sharon /Karen Thompson: mailgrams and clippings, 1988 (Box 196, Folder 12)
  - Kruse, Kitty: correspondence and printed material re: children's rights, 1992-94 (Box 196, Folder 13)
  - Landon, Michael: memorial foundation materials and letter from Cheryl Landon Wilson, undated (Box 196, Folder 14)
  - Laura X: correspondence and clippings, 1980-81 (Box 196, Folder 15)
  - Leaflets: miscellaneous subjects, undated (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - Liberty Club: correspondence and promotional materials, 1984 (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - Limbaugh, Rush: correspondence and clippings, 1992; 1994 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - Lists, undated (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - Louisiana Council on Human Relations: correspondence, 1980 (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - MacKinnon, Catharine: address transcript, 1982 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - Magazine Publishers Association, Inc.: Board of Directors minutes and related materials, including roster and bill, HR 7700, 1978 (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - Mailer, Norman: clippings, 1979 (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - Mamonova, Tatyana: correspondence, visa and employment materials, press release, printed material, and copy of TM's magazine Women and Earth: An Ecofeminist Almanac in English and Russian, 1995 (Box 197, Folder 9)
  - Manley, Wilma: correspondence, 1988-89 (Box 197, Folder 10)
  - March on Washington: correspondence, memoranda, brochure, 1983 (Box 197, Folder 11)
  - March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights: correspondence, press release, memoranda, reports, and budget, 1979 (Box 197, Folder 12)
  - March on Washington/ March for Women's Lives: memoir by Patricia Oliver, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 13)
  - Marchiano, Linda: clippings, correspondence, legal material (including amicus brief by Catharine MacKinnon), and notes, 1980; undated (Box 197, Folder 14-16)
  - Marciano, Linda: clippings, correspondence, legal material (including amicus brief by Catharine MacKinnon), and notes, 1980; undated (Box 198, Folder 1-3)
  - Martha Movement: correspondence, 1977 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - Martin, Grace B.: writings 1943, 1984, undated (includes inscribed copy of Postcard from Armageddon) (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Martin, Nell, "Self-Esteem for Women" weekend workshop: brochure, handbook, participant evaluation forms, endorsement by Steinem, and miscellany, 1992 (Box 198, Folder 6-7)
  - McCall, David: correspondence re: book, The Little Rascals: Child Sex Crimes in America, 1993-94 (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - McCorvey, Norma: clippings and memoranda, 1994-95 (Box 198, Folder 9)
  - McGovern, George: clippings and memoranda, 1994; 1996 (Box 198, Folder 10)
  - Men: clippings, 1971; undated (Box 198, Folder 11)
  - Men for ERA: notes and advertisement, undated (Box 198, Folder 12)
  - Mernissi, Fatima: papers, c.v., and book proposals, 1970; 1981; undated (Box 198, Folder 13)
  - Minorities in the U.S.: printed material, 1971; undated (Box 198, Folder 14)
  - Miscellany
    - Clippings, 1979-84; undated (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Mailings regarding "miscellaneous causes,", 1967-71 (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - Magazines, 1976-83 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Printed material, 1956-75 (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Moore, Sanford: correspondence, 1976 (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Moral Majority: correspondence, 1980 (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - Morgenstern, Carla: correspondence, 1988-95 (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - Moss, Ron: correspondence, clippings, and information regarding the African Medical and Research Foundation, 1977; 1979 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Municipal Art Society of New York: correspondence, memoranda, and brochure, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL): Board of Directors minutes, balance sheets, by-laws, clippings, correspondence, letter campaign 1979-88 (includes Steinem's letter to Ronald Reagan) (Box 199, Folder 8-10)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA): promotional literature and ad campaign (includes script of ad with Steinem and Charlton Heston), 1987 (Box 199, Folder 11)
  - National Committee on Household Employment: correspondence, agendas, minutes and memoranda, and organizing handbook and related materials, 1972-77 (Box 199, Folder 12)
  - National Congress of Neighborhood Women: letter and newsletter, 1976 (Box 199, Folder 13)
  - National Institute for Women of Color: correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 199, Folder 14)
  - National Organization for Women, Inc. (NOW): general, 1969-1974; 1992 (Box 199, Folder 15)
  - National Project on Ethnic America: correspondence and uncorrected galleys, 1973 (Box 199, Folder 16)
  - National Rural Fellows: brochure and correspondence, 1981 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - National Women's Education Fund: "Women's Political Options in 1982, 1984: A Preliminary Report," n.d. (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - National Women's Mailing List: promotional material, undated (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Native American Women: clipping and flyer, 1980 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - New Bedford Coalition Against Sexist Violence: correspondence, clippings, receipts, and itinerary, 1983 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - New England Circle: correspondence and printed material, 1974-80 (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - New Medium: letter and clippings, 1987 (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters, brochures and catalogs (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - NYC Commission on the Status of Women: reports, miscellany, 1971; 1973; 1980 (Box 200, Folder 9-10)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union: correspondence and "NYCLU Foundation Proposal for a Women's Rights Program,", 1985-86 (Box 200, Folder 11)
  - New York Life Insurance, 1978 (Box 200, Folder 12)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers: correspondence and printed material, 1994 (Box 200, Folder 13)
  - Nicaragua Education Project: correspondence, clippings, typescript, 1983 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - 9 to 5: miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Noble, Elaine: autobiographical manuscript, undated (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Nurses: correspondence and research materials on comparable worth, 1981-82 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Odyssey Institute: correspondence and press releases, 1977-80 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Old Lesbians Organizing for Change: correspondence and promotional material, 1994-95 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Older Women's League: OWL Observer Dec 1985, and thank-you card, Oct 1985 (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - Ono, Yoko: interview, 1984 (Box 201, Folder 8)
  - O'Reilly, Jane: correspondence, 1969 (Box 201, Folder 9)
  - Panthers: printed materials, 1967-69 (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - Pauciello-Rowe, Lisa: correspondence, photographs, slides, 1979 (Box 201, Folder 11)
  - Paul, Alice
    [see Alice Paul Foundation]
  - People magazine: correspondence and clippings re: interview, 1983 (Box 201, Folder 12)
  - "Personal Style" seminar: press packet and photographs of Steinem, others, 1983 (Box 201, Folder 12a)
  - PBS Panel: correspondence and memoranda, 1980 (Box 201, Folder 13)
  - Phillipines: proposal to promote trade and tourism, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 14)
  - Planned Parenthood: correspondence supporting Faye Wattleton for presidency, 1978 (Box 201, Folder 15)
  - Poetry (includes Rita Mae Brown and Margarita Castro) (Box 201, Folder 16)
  - Poets and Writers, Inc.: correspondence and newsletters, 1978-79 (Box 201, Folder 17)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund: correspondence and printed materials, 1974-77 (Box 201, Folder 18)
  - Pornography: clippings, correspondence, general material and material pertaining to Minneapolis ordinance (including Dworkin v. L.F.P., Inc.: complaint and press release), Andrea Dworkin's 1980 "Remarks on Women and Pornography," and writings by Steinem on snuff films, n.d. (Box 202, Folder 1-14)
  - Price, Meryl: correspondence and development materials regarding Showtime's "Best Friends .... Making A Difference,", 1994 (Box 202, Folder 15)
  - Project CEASE (Campaign to End all Sexism in Education): grant recommendation, 1981 (Box 202, Folder 16)
  - Project for Reproductive Freedom: correspondence, clippings, financial statement, 1979 (Box 202, Folder 17)
  - Pro-Choice Resource Center: correspondence and promotional material, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 18)
  - Pro-Life Curriculum (Nebraska), 1980 (Box 202, Folder 19)
  - Psychiatrists for ERA: correspondence, press release, 1981 (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Public Assistance and Social Service: reports, studies, miscellany, 1969-73 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - Pudge: correspondence with Lee Marrs, cartoons, and review by Steinem, 1974-80 (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - Puerto Rican community in New York, 1969 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - Qing, Jiang: press advisories, clipping, 1981 (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - Quotes (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - Racism (Marguerite Gamble): clipping and press materials (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - Radical/alternative politics: printed material, 1967; undated (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - Ragghianti, Marie: correspondence, clippings, manuscript, 1983; 1985 (Box 203, Folder 11)
  - Raphael House: memoranda and press materials, 1994 (Box 203, Folder 12)
  - Reagan, Ronald, advertisement: correspondence, notes and text of New York Times ad, 1980 (Box 203, Folder 13)
  - Reagan, Ronald and the New Right: notes and clippings, 1980-81 (Box 203, Folder 14)
  - Redford, Robert: correspondence and clippings, 1974; 1985-86; undated (Box 203, Folder 15)
  - Redstockings allegations (Box 203, Folder 16-19)
  - Religion: notes, articles, clippings, 1978-80 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Reproductive Freedom Newsletter, 1983 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Resumes (Box 204, Folder 3-5)
  - Rosenberg, Carol Smith: paper, undated (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Rural American Women: correspondence and press materials, 1979 (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - Rural Development Leadership Network: correspondence, newsletters, 1990 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - Saul, Rose: notes and article, 1971 (Box 204, Folder 9)
  - Screw: correspondence, clippings, full issues, 1973 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - "Season of Shame": correspondence, outline, scripts, contract, 1988-89 (Box 205, Folder 2-3)
  - Service Employees International Union: press materials, 1982 (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - Sex role socialization: paper by Lenore Weitzman, 1972 (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - Sexual harassment: correspondence and printed materials, 1975-81 (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - Shalala, Donna: speech, 1983 (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - Sheet music, 1977 (Box 205, Folder 8)
  - Shigekawa, Joan: correspondence, resume, 1983-84 (Box 205, Folder 9)
  - Simmons College Advisory Committee of the Graduate Program in Management: correspondence and meeting materials, 1975; 1977 (Box 205, Folder 10)
  - Simpson, Nicole Brown: clippings, 1995 (Box 205, Folder 11)
  - Sloan, Margaret: correspondence, clipping, financial materials, and notes 1971-73 [restricted] (Box 205, Folder 12)
  - Smith College: correspondence, clippings, 1973; 1986 (Box 206, Folder 1-2)
  - Smith, Susan: clippings, 1995 (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Smithsonian Women's Council: correspondence and memoranda, 1978 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Society for the Right to Die: minutes and clippings, 1985-86 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - Sojourner: correspondence, investors reports, issue, 1977-78 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Sojourner Truth statuette (commercial): photo and promotional material, 1986 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - Soo Hoo Lee Productions: prospectus and note, 1977 (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - Southern Mutual Help Association (Louisiana): notes and correspondence, 1980 (Box 206, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Women: correspondence and paper (Box 206, Folder 10)
  - Speeches (not by Steinem): Ivy Bottini on lesbianism as a feminist issue 1973; Marlo Thomas' address before the National Secretaries Convention, 1980; Mim Kelber before Association of Radical Historians, 1980 (Box 206, Folder 11)
  - Stark, Ray: correspondence and letters of agreement re: "The Cleaning Lady,", 1989 (Box 206, Folder 12)
  - Stewardesses for Women's Rights: conference packet and clippings, 1974 (Box 206, Folder 13)
  - Sterilization: clippings, notes, writings, 1973-75; undated (Box 206, Folder 14-16)
  - Straus, Jane: correspondence and funeral program, 1980 (Box 206, Folder 17)
  - Students Organizing Students: correspondence, 1995 (Box 206, Folder 18)
  - Supersisters Cards: promotional flyer, undated (Box 206, Folder 19)
  - Surrogacy: correspondence, press releases, and clippings, 1987-89 (Box 206, Folder 20)
  - Sweden: U.N. report on "The Status of Women in Sweden," 1968, and Herta, 1969 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - Synectics: promotional material, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - Taylor, Elizabeth: articles, 1978 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Theater (New Georges): correspondence, memoranda, and clippings 1992-93 (includes endorsing blurb by Steinem) (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - Third world women; correspondence, writings, and miscellany (includes press statement by Kate Millett on women in Spain), 1974; 1978-79; undated (Box 207, Folder 5-6)
  - Thomas, Franklin: article, 1985 (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Time Leadership Conference: packet, 1976 (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - Tobias, Sheila: article on leadership, 1970 (Box 207, Folder 9)
  - Torture of women in Chile: correspondence, clippings and press material, 1974-75 (Box 207, Folder 10)
  - Transafrica: correspondence and script re: 25th anniversary tribute to Peter, Paul and Mary, 1986 (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - TransWorld Airlines: Independent Federation of Flight Attendants correspondence and strike materials, 1986 (Box 207, Folder 12)
  - Unions, 1980-83 (Box 207, Folder 13)
  - United Farm Workers: clippings, correspondence (includes Cesar Chavez), press releases, 1968-74; 1985; undated (Box 207, Folder 14)
  - United Farm Workers: clippings, correspondence (includes Cesar Chavez), press releases, 1968-74; 1985; undated (Box 208, Folder 1-6)
  - United Nations Economic and Social Council: report from World Population conference, 1974 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - Vernon-Roe, Vivien: correspondence, 1989 (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - Volunteers in Service to America: correspondence and informational packet, 1980 (Box 208, Folder 9)
  - "Waiting Tables" (documentary): correspondence and promotional material, 1983-85 (Box 208, Folder 10)
  - Washingtonian: issue, March 1979 (Box 208, Folder 11)
  - WDIV Channel 4: clippings and press releases about sexist program "Three's A Crowd,", 1979 (Box 208, Folder 12)
  - Welfare: clippings, correspondence, press advisories, printed material, 1971; 1977; 1979 (Box 209, Folder 1-5)
  - Wheaton College/Coretta Scott King: correspondence, 1974 (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - White House Fellows Program: public relations material, undated (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - WICCA: correspondence, printed material, writings, research papers, 1977 (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - Wollstonecraft, Inc.: business plan, 1973 (Box 209, Folder 9)
  - Women Against Violence Against Women: correspondence, press releases, clippings, 1976-79 (Box 209, Folder 10)
  - Women Against Violence in Pornography and Media (San Francisco): notes reports, correspondence, circa, 1979 (Box 209, Folder 11)
  - "Women and the Constitution:" symposium materials, 1988 (Box 209, Folder 12)
  - Women and Aging: "Uncharted Territory: Issues and Concerns of Women over 40," University of Maryland Center on Aging report, 1978 (Box 209, Folder 13)
  - Women and Building: newsletter, 1972 (Box 209, Folder 14)
  - Women and development: correspondence, proposals, article, 1977-80 (Box 209, Folder 15)
  - Women and economics: notes, articles, printed material, 1970-73 (Box 209, Folder 16)
  - Women and food: articles, notes, writings, circa, 1979 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Women and journalism (includes complaint against Time for failing to promote women to writing position), 1970 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Women and music: general (includes "A Chronology of Songs by Women," 1862-1976), 1986-87; undated (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Women and Nazi Germany: notes and articles, 1973-80; undated (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Women and poverty: report, 1969 (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Women and religion: correspondence, printed material, 1977-80 (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Women and science: article, 1974 (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - Women and work: notes, clippings, printed material, 1973; 1984; undated (Box 210, Folder 8)
  - "Women Are Good News": correspondence, 1992 (Box 210, Folder 9)
  - Women in Arab Countries: correspondence and clippings, 1970-78 (Box 210, Folder 10)
  - Women in Europe: general, 1968; 1971 (Box 210, Folder 11)
  - Women in journalism: Nieman Report, 1979 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Women in media: notes, correspondence, and Annenberg Report, "Women and Minorities in Television Drama 1969-1978, " 1986 (Box 211, Folder 2-3)
  - Women in midlife: general (includes Eleanor Smeal's 1979 congressional testimony on aging), 1974 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Women in production: correspondence, 1990 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Women office workers: correspondence and printed matter, 1978; undated (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - The Women's Building: project overview, clippings, correspondence, 1993-94 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Women's Campaign Fund: correspondence, memoranda, minutes, press releases, 1976-77 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - Women's Caucus for Art: notes, press material, 1984 (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Women's Funding Coalition: correspondence, 1985-86 (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - Women's History
    - Checklist, "Ancient to 1700 ", in Dissertation Abstracts, 1979 (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Clippings, 1970; undated (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - National Women's History Slideshow: correspondence, 1992 (Box 211, Folder 13)
  - Women's Liberation
    - Academic articles, 1970; 1975; undated (Box 211, Folder 14)
    - Booklets, 1970; 1978; undated (Box 211, Folder 15)
    - Clippings
      - 1960s-70, 1960s-70s (Box 211, Folder 16-17)
      - 1980s-90 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Flyers (includes "No More Miss America!"), 1970 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - General 1967-73, undated (includes sheet music for "Liberation, Now!") (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Legal memorandum: "The Case for Equality in State Jury Services," prepared for the ACLU by Pauli Murray and Dorothy Kenyon, 1966 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous newsletters, 1970-76 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Women's Liberation Center: press release, undated (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Women's Lobby: correspondence, 1974-79 (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - Women's Rights Law Reporter:, Spring/Summer; 1977 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Women's Rights Park, Seneca Falls: correspondence, 1980 (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Women's Studies: course syllabi, 1970; undated (Box 212, Folder 10)
  - Women's Talent Bank: note, letter from White House, 1971 (Box 212, Folder 11)
  - Women's Trusteeship: membership list and report, 1984; undated (Box 212, Folder 12)
  - Women's Way: correspondence, newsletters, brochures, conference material, 1986-90 (Box 213, Folder 1-3)
  - Women Writers' Conference: conference packet 1987 (includes clippings re: Marilyn) (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Wonder Woman: correspondence, comics, 1970-72 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - Woodhull, Victoria (documentary): correspondence, 1994-95 (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - Working women: clippings, correspondence, newsletters, 1978-80 (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - Working Women Education Fund: progress report, undated (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - Working Women United Institute: correspondence, press materials, 1978 (Box 213, Folder 9)
  - Writers' Guild of America: members' mailings, 1983-85 (Box 213, Folder 10)
  - Zuckerman, Mort: clippings, 1975-85 (Box 213, Folder 11)
- SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS, 1940s-90s